<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resource>    PrometiumBooster SalePackApocalypse Booty KeyA hacked key designed to open the Apocalypse Booty Boxes, containing a variety of things to tempt the finest pilots!This Apocalypse Booty Key opens the highly vauled Apocalypse Booty Boxes, stuffed to the brim with exciting treasures.APOC KeyBOOTY KEYCapsuleUse these capsules to enter the lottery during the Hitac event, and you could win amazing prizes!Capsule BlueprintHitac LotteryPrometheus Sale BonanzaCelebrate the souls of the Prometheus by grabbing one of the exclusive packs in the Prometheus Sale Bonanza!Prometheus Sale BonanzaSale     Drawing entryEntry for participating in drawing.EntryXTM Test Key in the file resource_items.xmlOnly one of these items is allowed per configuration.Design PackDESIGN PACKSkill designSKILL DESIGNHH-XWith a hangar hall, you can quickly switch ships while at your headquarters, or even when logged out. &lt;li&gt;You may expand your hangar to include up to &lt;b&gt;10 HH-X&lt;/b&gt;s.&lt;/li&gt;HH-XHANGAR EXPANSION    S-OS-01Classic Collector's Sale&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rediscover refurbished classic ships in this exclusive offer for the discerning collector. They don't make them like this any more! Admire the lines of these limited edition, hard to find, and discontinued ships - Yamato and Defcom are back!Yamato and Defcom ShipsPackS-DS-01State of the Art Sale&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lunar Industries, Titan Technologies, and the Kepler Foundries have all come together to create unprecedented deals for the discerning pilot who demands the best. Combining next-gen techniques and ultra-modern styling, these ships are being offered at astonishing prices.Super Ship SelectionPackD-RavenSwoop down upon your prey in the classic Defcom Raven. The sweeping lines of the ship disguise its enhanced HP and cloaking ability. Ready to shock the enemy on arrival.Defcom RavenShipY-RoninBe the lone warrior in the pack with the Yamato Ronin. The technicians have made a significant overhaul of this ships HP, making you harder to kill in conflict.Yamato RoninShipG-IgniteA rare gem matching the design of the ships, which fought and won the second Sibelon War of 2727. Relive past glories, fly the flag of humanity and ride into battle with this paragon of mankind!Goliath IgniteShipN-AmbassadorBe the VIP of your faction with the Nostromo Ambassador. The ship that helped seal the Crystal Truce of 2641 is now yours. Ready to add a touch of class, diplomacy and still be a powerful vessel in battle.Nostromo AmbassadorShipDD-RB-02Robo-bat design color variations&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This drone design will make your drones look like threatening Robo-bats! Pick your favorite color, give your drones a trail, and stand out from the crowd!Robo-bat Drone ColorsCosmetic Design PackDD-S-02Skull drone design color variations&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This drone design will make your drones look like bone-chilling Skulls! Pick your favorite color, give your drones a trail, and stand out from the crowd!Skull Drone ColorsCosmetic Design PackDD-R-02Reaper drone design color variations&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This drone design will make your drones look like sinister Reapers! Pick your favorite color, give your drones a trail, and stand out from the crowd!Reaper Drone ColorsCosmetic Design PackDD-F-01Imbue your drones with the newest Ice meteoroid technology! This design will only alter the look of your drones!Hailstorm DroneCosmetic DesignDD-PC-01Although they have now been eradicated, M.A.S.Q.U.E.'s cutting-edge technology still makes an impression! Give your insipid workhorse drones the look of a fireworks display in Blaze, Sandstorm or Borealis!Awesome M.A.S.Q.U.E. DroneCosmetic Design PackP.E.T. Design PackCosmetic P.E.T. designs as far as the radar's eye can see! Now the Arctic, Red, and Green P.E.T. designs can all be yours. Stand out from the crowd!Arctic, Red and Green P.E.T.Cosmetic Design PackGreen ChimeraM.A.S.Q.U.E.'s P.E.T. designs were winners across the board. Grab the Chimera design in green, and bring a touch of natures bounty to space.Green Chimera P.E.T.Cosmetic DesignOrange ChimeraThanks to M.A.S.Q.U.E., your P.E.T. can be an orange Chimera - ready to take on this world or any other. Bring a dab of color to the darkness of deep space!Orange Chimera P.E.T.Cosmetic DesignRed ChimeraDragonfire! Friend and foe alike will be speechless before this Chimera design for your P.E.T. - look for the genuine article, now in dragon-red!Red Chimera P.E.T.Cosmetic DesignThe Red BoxDo you have a fiery temperament and the aesthetic to match? Then this fabulous offer from M.A.S.Q.U.E. is meant for you! Get the snazzy Chimera P.E.T. design along with 10 Phantom designs for your drones, both (of course) in flaming red!The Red BoxCosmetic Design PackTartarus SetA completionist collector’s delight! Fly off with the Tartarus ship, 10 Phantom drone designs, and 1 Chimera P.E.T. design – the full matched set painted in Blaze!Tartarus Ship, P.E.T. and DroneSetPoison A-Elite SetA space ship enthusiast's delight! Fly off with a special design for your Aegis Elite, as well as 10 A-Elite drone designs and an A-Elite P.E.T. design, all painted in Poison!Poison A-Elite Ship, P.E.T. and DroneSetPoison Pusat SetA space ship enthusiast's delight! Fly off with a terrific design for your Pusat and 10 Pusat drone designs all painted in Poison!Poison Pusat Ship, P.E.T. and DroneSetPoison Spectrum SetA space ship enthusiast's delight! Fly off with a terrific design for your Spectrum, and 10 Spectrum drone designs all painted in Poison!Poison Spectrum Ship, P.E.T. and DroneSetBlaze Spectrum SetA space ship enthusiast's delight! Fly off with a special design for your Spectrum, as well as 10 Spectrum drone designs and a Spectrum P.E.T. design, all painted in Blaze!Blaze Spectrum Ship, P.E.T. and DroneSetBlaze Pusat SetA space ship enthusiast's delight! Fly off with a special design for your Pusat, as well as 10 Pusat drone designs and a Pust P.E.T. design, all painted in Blaze!Blaze Pusat Ship, P.E.T. and DroneSetFrozen MirageSend an icy chill down your enemies’ spine with the Frozen Mirage Pack. This chillingly valuable pack contains all the artic designs for the Spectrum, Sentinel, Venom, V-Lightning, Pusat and N-Ambassador.Frozen Mirage Ship SkinsCosmetic Design PackSpectrum ChromaPick your true colour of Spectrum from the much vaunted Spectrum Chroma Pack at a highly desirable price. Each pack contains the Poison, Sandstorm, Blaze and Ocean Spectrum designs.Spectrum Chroma Ship SkinsCosmetic Design PackPusat ChromaGet the pack with Poison, Sandstorm, Blaze and Ocean Pusat designs all in one place. The highly prized Pusat Chroma pack is available now at a highly sought after price.Pusat Chroma Ship SkinsCosmetic Design PackPhantom ChimeraThe Phantom Chimera Pack is just bursting with Phantom and Chimera designs, at a fabulous price. Deals like this can't last forever.Phantom Chimera Ship SkinsCosmetic Design PackFine Design Packs!A fabulous selection of designs available for all pilots of Venom, Solace and Aegis Elite vessels. Limited Offer!Fine Ship SkinsCosmetic Design PackStriking DesignsSpectrum and Pusat owners can get a classic set of designs for their ships, with the all new Poison P.E.T. designs for both ships. Take a bite!Striking SkinsCosmetic Design PackBest SubscriptionsYou have a unique chance to get all popular subscriptions in this ultimate subscriptions bundle. This is a one-time limited offer, check it out now!DEALDealReady-to-FightWe have prepared a unique bundle offer including a Goliath spaceship and some powerful equipment! This is a one-time limited offer, go check it out now!DEALDealSilver Booty KeyRight now - and for a limited time only - you can acquire silver Booty Keys, which allow you to open Silver Booty Boxes. You'll have the chance to find Aegis, Citadel or Spearhead Ship Designs, LF-4, or Drone Designs, as well as other great prizes!DEALBooty KeyRed Booty KeyAvailable now for a limited time only - the Red Booty Key deal. Act now and take advantage of this unbelievable doubled chance at getting your own LF-4 laser.DEALBooty KeyBlue Booty KeyAvailable now for a limited time only - the Blue Booty Key deal. Act now and take advantage of this unbelievable threefold chance at getting your own LF-4 laser.DEALBooty KeyP.E.T.Available for a limited time only - the P.E.T. Deal. Get in on this special offer now and enjoy up to 55% savings!DEALDealExtra EnergyThe extra energy deal - now available for a limited time. Act now and profit from these incredible offers with savings of upto 56%!DEALDealJump CouponThe jump coupon deal - now available for a limited time only. Act now and profit from these incredible offers with savings of up to 56%!DEALDealLog-diskThe log-disk deal: Available now for a limited time only. Act now and rake in up to 160% savings with this unbelievable offer!DEALDealBooty KeyThe booty key deal: Available now and only for a limited time. Act now and rake in up to 160% savings with this unbelievable offer!DEALDealUpgrade VoucherAvailable for a limited time only - the Upgrade Voucher Deal. Act now and enjoy the 100% chances of success when upgrading your items!DEALDealSadece 1,5 TLGrab this unique package with most rare and useful boosters for just a handful of pennies. You’ll get:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;DMG-B02 Damage booster (+10% damage, 10 hours, works for the group)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SHD-B02 Shield Booster (+25% shield, 10 hours, works for the group)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hp-B02 Hitpoints Booster (+10% hitpoints, 10 hours, works for the group)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;with an incredible discount!KAMPANYASadece 1,5 TLSuper BoosterGrab this unique package with most rare and useful boosters for just a handful of pennies. You’ll get:&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;DMG-B02 Damage booster (+10% damage, 10 hours, works for the group)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SHD-B02 Shield Booster (+25% shield, 10 hours, works for the group)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hp-B02 Hitpoints Booster (+10% hitpoints, 10 hours, works for the group)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;with an incredible discount!SBP-01PackTournament AmmoSpecial packs of boosters and ammo – hurry before they're gone! Whether you prefer to fly aggressively, defensively, or both, you can pounce on an amazing deal tailored for you, featuring limited availability items for a fantastic price.TR-SP-01PackUltra Booty Secret SaleBrought to you by the Helix: don't miss out on the new Ultra versions of Red and Blue Booty, along with a tripled chance at excellent prizes!U-RB-01Booty KeyUltra Booty Secret SaleBrought to you by the Helix: don't miss out on the new Ultra versions of Red and Blue Booty, along with a tripled chance at excellent prizes!U-RB-01Booty KeyCapsuleUse these capsules to enter the lottery during the Hitac event, and you could win amazing prizes!Capsule BlueprintHitac Lottery    </resource>
